<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FOR DEVELOPERS on Welcome to stegos!</title>
    <link>/docs/for-developers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FOR DEVELOPERS on Welcome to stegos!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/docs/for-developers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building from Source</title>
      <link>/docs/for-developers/building_from_source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/for-developers/building_from_source/</guid>
      <description>Building on Linux and Mac Requirements  Stegos requires Rust 1.38.0-nightly (d3f8a0b5d 2019-08-04) to build. The recommended way to install Rust it to use rustup. If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have rustup, you can install it like this: curl https://sh.rustup.rs -sSf | sh Make sure that these binaries are in your PATH. After that, you should be able to build Stegos from the source. Use nightly-2019-08-04 toolchain when asked. libflint and libgmp - we expect libflint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Directory Layout</title>
      <link>/docs/for-developers/data_directory_layout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/for-developers/data_directory_layout/</guid>
      <description>Data directory has the following layout:
1 ├── accounts/ &amp;lt;!-- Accounts 2 │ ├── 1 3 │ │ ├── account.pkey &amp;lt;!-- Account #1 public key (address) 4 │ │ ├── account.skey &amp;lt;!-- Account #2 secret key (address) 5 │ │ └── history/ &amp;lt;!-- Payment History (RocksDB) 6 │ └── 2 7 │ ├── account.pkey &amp;lt;!-- Account #1 public key (address) 8 │ ├── account.skey &amp;lt;!-- Account #2 secret key (address) 9 │ └── history/ &amp;lt;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebSocket API</title>
      <link>/docs/for-developers/websocket_api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/docs/for-developers/websocket_api/</guid>
      <description>Stegos Node offers experimental asynchronous WebSocket API. This API allow you to manage accounts, create and track transactions, receive notifications and so on.
 Prerequisites Protocol  Framing Payload Remote Procedure Calls Notifications  Wallet RPC API  List Accounts Create Account Delete Account Getting Recovery Phrase Recover Account Unseal Account Seal Account Account Information Change Password Account Information Balance Information UTXO Information Payment Cloak Stake Unstake Restake Validate Certificate Payment History  Wallet Notifications  Balance Changed Tokens Received Tokens Spent Tokens Staked Tokens Unstaked Transaction Status Snowball Status  Node RPC API  Escrow Information Election Information Enable Restaking Pop Block  Node Notifications  Synchronization Status Changed New Micro Block Rollback Micro Block New Macro Block  Use Cases  Transaction Tracking   Prerequisites  Node is up and running Any WebSocket client library or a browser.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>