<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CLI WALLET on Welcome to stegos!</title><link>/cli_wallet/</link><description>Recent content in CLI WALLET on Welcome to stegos!</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/cli_wallet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Quick Start</title><link>/cli_wallet/quick_start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cli_wallet/quick_start/</guid><description>Use stegos/stegosDocker image to start Node: docker run -v $PWD/stegos-data:/data --name stegos_node -t -i stegos/stegos Execute stegos command inside container to get into CLI: docker exec -t -i stegos_node stegos CLI will prompt for commands: Stegos CLI 0.11.13 (e63fb9e 2019-08-09) Type &amp;#39;help&amp;#39; to get help stegos&amp;gt; Type create account to create a new account: account#1&amp;gt; create account Enter new password: Enter same password again: --- - type: account_created account_id: &amp;#34;1&amp;#34; .</description></item><item><title>Installing a node</title><link>/cli_wallet/installing_a_node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cli_wallet/installing_a_node/</guid><description>In this section we explain how to install Stegos Node (stegosd) and Stegos Command-Line Client (stegos) on your server.
Prerequisites:
Linux host (any distro) OR macOS host OR Docker-enabled host. Installing on Linux For production purposes, we recommend official binaries from GitHub Release page. These binaries have been tested on 64-bit versions of Ubuntu 18.04 &amp;ldquo;Bionic&amp;rdquo;, Debian 11 &amp;ldquo;Stretch&amp;rdquo; and Fedora 30. Other Linux distros should work as well.</description></item><item><title>Running a Node</title><link>/cli_wallet/running_a_node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cli_wallet/running_a_node/</guid><description>In this section we explain how to run Stegos Node.
Prerequisites:
Download and install Stegos Node. Run Stegos Node:
Stegos Node will automatically create a data directory to store the blockchain and your accounts:
INFO [stegosd] Data directory: /home/yourname/.local/share/stegos The default path to the data directory depends on your operating system:
On the first run, the blockchain database is initialized using the genesis block for testnet network:
INFO [stegosd] Using genesis=14427eb426e3 for &amp;#39;testnet&amp;#39; chain devnet- development (alpha) network testnet- test (beta) network mainnet- production network (soon!</description></item><item><title>Connecting to a Node</title><link>/cli_wallet/connection_to_a_node/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cli_wallet/connection_to_a_node/</guid><description>In this section we explain how to connect to a Stegos Node.
Prerequisites:
Node is up and running Connecting to a Local Node The command-line client will try to connect to a local node and print stegos prompt on success:
1Stegos CLI 0.11.13 (e63fb9e 2019-08-09) 2Type &amp;#39;help&amp;#39; to get help 3 4account#1&amp;gt; Type help to get help:
1stegos&amp;gt; help 2Usage: 3show accounts - show available accounts 4use ACCOUNT_ID - switch to a account 5create account - add a new account 6recover account - recover account from 24-word recovery phrase 7delete account - delete active account 8passwd - change account&amp;#39;s password 9lock - lock the account 10unlock - unlock the account 11 12pay ADDRESS AMOUNT [COMMENT] [/snowball] [/public] [/lock DATETIME] [/fee FEE] [/certificate] - send money 13validate certificate UTXO SENDER_ADDRESS RECIPIENT_ADDRESS RVALUE - check that payment certificate is valid 14msg ADDRESS MESSAGE - send a message via blockchain 15stake AMOUNT - stake money 16unstake [AMOUNT] - unstake money 17restake - restake all available stakes 18cloak - exchange all available public outputs 19show version - print version information 20show keys - print keys 21show balance - print balance 22show utxo - print unspent outputs 23show history [STARTING DATE] - print history since date 24show election - print leader election state 25show escrow - print escrow 26show recovery - print recovery information Connecting to a Remote Node Copy api.</description></item><item><title>Last Steps</title><link>/cli_wallet/last_steps/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cli_wallet/last_steps/</guid><description>Congratulations! If you have made it this far, you belong to a tiny group of people on this planet who knows how to run a blockchain node.
Please join us on Telegram Chat to get test tokens and let us know your thoughts. Subscribe to official Telegram Channel for the latest news.</description></item><item><title>Working with Accounts</title><link>/cli_wallet/working_with_accounts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/cli_wallet/working_with_accounts/</guid><description>Creating an Account Type create account to create a new account. You will be asked for a password. This password is used locally to encrypt your data on the disk. Please remember it.
Type show recovery to get 24-word recovery phrase. This recovery phrase is an encoded representation of your secret key. Please write down it and keep it in a safe place. There are no other password recovery mechanisms.</description></item></channel></rss>